<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[mrbromley]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[mrbromley]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/mrbromley/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 19:26:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/mrbromley/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[London to Beijing on the Trans-Mongolian Railway]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>London to Beijing on the Trans-Mongolian Railway</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8255f5213a83be1d5d12c7f9c1bce93d167bb0f0.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/mrbromley/26bccbdc-c3f2-492a-b451-618ba2035332/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">26bccbdc-c3f2-492a-b451-618ba2035332</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 19:21:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[San Francisco to Boston on Amtrak]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>San Francisco to Boston on Amtrak</h1><p>I woke up in Cleveland, this was only distinguishable from the croocked glow of its, surely beloved, football stadium sign. It took a few minutes to recall why I was here at 4 o'clock in the morning. Seven hours eairlier I had witnessed mild déjà Vue as I once again boarded a mile long crosscountry Amtrak train at Chicago's Union Station four months after my initial departure from the same gate, only this time my journey was heading East towards Boston.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/mrbromley/san-francisco-to-boston-on-amtrack/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">311c81f0-639c-4c1d-acb0-6ccc89823667</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 19:18:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Freediving with Legends]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Freediving with Legends</h1><p>Sitting waterside on the dock at one of the few established restaurants in Karelendike's small port watching young Dutch couples walk the boulevard in the warm night air and just inches below the dock the glow of a marine light highlights the pure ocean below diners feet, it's a casual affair some tourists dress up a little as they spend their last evening under the stars sipping their mojitos. It's also one of the few places to get a decent wifi signal and as I finish another run and coke I hit the call on Skype the number takes a few seconds to connect when a screeching on the line disturbs the natural calm that had descended on the dock since the sun slipped away a few hours ago. An instantly recognisable voice finally comes through over some dying digital static, 'where you are?' this slightly commanding yet overtly friendly Spanglish is the first I've heard from Carlos in two days, he reassures me that the choice of restaurant was well made and congratulates me on my arrival to the island, with little small talk we arrange to meet at 3 o'clock the following day. Enough time to settle in to my new home and get prepared, after all it's not every day I arrange to meet a world record holder and champion athlete.  </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/mrbromley/freediving-with-legends/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">48d4512e-7ec5-47b0-aa9c-3cda0bf97bb2</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 19:25:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>